S_0001.seq
0,PS_0001.EOV,0,Powered by Rutronik

S_0002.seq
0,PS_0002.EOV,1,CO2 Concentration is normal

S_0003.seq
0,PS_0003.EOV,2,CO2 Concentration is higher than normal. The environment should be vented

S_0004.seq
0,PS_0004.EOV,3,CO2 Concentration is critically high. Please leave the area ASAP

S_0005.seq
0,PS_0005.EOV,4,CO2 Concentration has reached the workplace exposure limit. Please leave the area immediately.

S_0006.seq
0,PS_0006.EOV,5,CO2 Concentration is deadly high. Leave the area immediately

S_0007.seq
0,PS_0007.EOV,6,motion detected

